このまま戻らなかったら ４人のデータ 全部　消えちゃうわね。
I can no longer think of him... as a target to destroy.
まっ　ゴレイヌからの 連絡を待つしかないな。
He acknowledged our efforts.
よし　バッチリ！
He wasn't a bad guy.
ねぇ　もう百発百中だよ！ 放出系の修行に集中しても いいでしょ？
In that case, I no longer have...
ダメ！
any reason to defeat him.
百発百中っつっても 誤差が０．１秒くらいあるだろ？
The King...
理想は　０．０１秒以内。
The soldiers are not important.
はい　始め！ ちぇ。
If the King waves his baton, the soldiers
will become demons if necessary.
バッテラを連れて逃げたのが その証拠だ。
This is an area used for testing weapons of war.
だが　長年かけて９６種まで カードを集めたんだぜ？
We won't need to restrain ourselves.
推測の話をいくらしても仕方ない。
Why do you fight?
おっ　３時１０分　時間だ。
You have no chance of defeating me.
イェイ！ ツェズゲラ　バイバイ！
Why rush to your death?
３０種ぐらいは 偽物と交換してある。
You presume to know I cannot win?
実際の９６種を抱えてるのは　俺。
You know nothing about me.
慎重なツェズゲラ 一世一代の大冒険だ。
If you judge me by my appearance, you'll get burned.
悪いが　ゲンスルーとお前達が 戦うことになっても
You have it backwards.
分かってる 約束のカード　いつ取りに来る？
You don't seem like some ordinary man
who can't read the state of the battle.
お前達がゲンスルーを 倒した後でいいさ　頑張れよ。
I was born to rule this world.
予定は狂ったが　「一坪の海岸線」も 奴らから頂こう。
Originally, you humans were as
no more than livestock to me.
まずは 「アカンパニー」の調達だな。
But I have changed my mind.
ＯＫ。 奴らが動いた！ お前達　今どこだ？
I learned that there are a few
humans worth keeping alive.
ソウフラビの近く。 奴らは　マサドラの方角。
Like that woman.
準備は　いいか？ バッチリさ あんた達のおかげだよ。
I sense that you are worthy, as well.
時間が足りない でも　やるしかない あとは　ゴン次第 ゴン！ まさか　今の話に気をとられて
If you back down now, I am willing to spare your life.
失礼とは思いましたが 先程　拝借してまいりました。
Given my position, I can't accept that offer.
恋人だ。 長く入院していた。
Meanwhile...
ずっと意識がなかったが 先日　眠るように息を引き取った。
In exchange for his agreement to stay still, Pouf was pressing Pitou to explain
just what had happened.
拙い手作りの 写真立てなどを喜んだ。
Pitou complied with Pouf's request, telling
him what happened after the attack.
一緒になろうと 誓い合った矢先だった。 事故で…
Pitou made it a point to include
details that Gon did not know, to ensure that Gon's attention would
be focused on the explanation.
彼女は　いつ覚めるとも分からない 眠りについた。
Pitou deliberately did not mention
how the King had held Komugi
本当に…。 ただ　眠ってるように見えた。
because Pitou did not know how to
describe the events accurately.
そんな時 『グリードアイランド』の噂を聞いたんだ。
There was no significant change in Gon.
今の私に必要な 夢のようなアイテムが
However...
そのゲームをクリアすれば 手に入ると。
Pitou knew the plan had succeeded
when Gon's eyes wavered briefly.
全財産をなげうつ覚悟で ゲームを手に入れた。
The King...
だが　もういい…。
left with the enemy of his own
volition, by that doorway.
もういいんだ。
There is no need for us to go.
ガキどもは 全部で「アカンパニー」４回分。
I see. He went south.
こっちは６枚あるし　行くか？
I understand.
ああ。 いつでもいいぜ。
A fine play, Pitou.
黒トンガリのガキは俺が相手する。 腕ずくの交渉になったらの 話だがな。 サブは　つり目　バラは女を頼む。
Then we should await the King's return here.
何の用だ!? そんなに　とんがるなよ 取引に来たんだ。
To maintain only my outward appearance,
I only need one-seventh of my flies.
取引？　こっちにはないね！
The other six-sevenths
そう…　悟られてはいけない こちらが準備万端で 待ち構えていたことを
will go to the King!
そう　それでいい 私達は圧倒的に弱い立場を 演じなければならない
You fight with the resolve to lose?
あの場所へは　追い詰められて たどり着いた
I do not understand.
そんな印象を 奴らに与えなければ…
You fight for the human race?
話ってのはシンプルだ。 俺達が　みんなを代表してクリアし 全員で現実へ戻り
If so, then know that my actions
are, in fact, for their benefit.
バッテラからの報酬を山分けする。 とても信じられないね。 心を入れ替えたのさ。
For example, in human society, lands are divided by national borders,
much like territorial marking.
事実　ツェズゲラは もうゲームの外だぜ？
On the right side of the border,
children may starve to death.
けど　それが　あんたらの話に 乗った証拠にはならない！ そりゃ　まぁ　そうだな。
While on the left, scum who do nothing
have everything they need.
じゃ　どうする…　死ぬか？
Absolute madness.
ゴチャゴチャ言わずに カードをよこせ！ てめぇら全員ぶっ殺すぞ！
I shall crush that madness...
早速　正体　現しやがったぜ！ ブック！　「アカンパニー」オン！ ソウフラビへ！
And create a world so fair, the very concept of inequality will be forgotten!
マサドラ!?
I will initially use power and terror
to accomplish my objective.
スペルカードを補給する気か？ 港から現実へ逃げる気かもしれん。
But I will only do so to the extent
necessary to maintain order. I have learned what power
is meant to be used for.
気配を消して隠れたか？ 店をチェックだ。 スペルカードを買われたら 厄介だからな。
To protect the weak, who deserve to live.
来てないな。 もう港に向かったか？
Power is not meant to be used
to torment the defeated!
見失うなよ　こっちも 「アカンパニー」は　もうない！
This could be a problem... I shall not fight you.
あ…。 あっ！
I agreed to leave the palace
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 さぁ　もう諦めて カードをよこしたら　どうだ？
so we could have a free, open discussion.
嫌だね　絶対渡すもんか！
He's wavering...
予想通り　奴らは マンツーマンで戦う気だわね
Come closer. Wavering between Ant and human.
渡すくらいなら　やってやる！ おい　ゴン！
And he hasn't realized
クソ！ いいぞ　あとは少しずつ 奴らを引き離す
that those two sides are incompatible.
ビスケ！　お前は逃げろ！ でも…。
And neither one
いいから行け！ 待て！
is dominant yet.
おっと　逃がさねえぞ！ 頼むよ　２人とも！ お前の相手は俺だ!!
But regardless of which side he falls to, the outcome won't change.
お前 俺がボマーだと知っているな？ ツェズゲラに聞いた。 ほう…。
The immediate extermination
of these dangerous creatures. There have already been many casualties. We will use any means necessary.
で　俺の能力は　誰に聞いた？
Will that be acceptable?
すごい たった一瞬の動きでバレた
Naturally, we have no intention of
telling the experts how to proceed.
俺が警戒していること その背景
We simply desire
これが　戦闘経験の差！
those dangerous creatures
eradicated as swiftly as possible.
そう多くはないはずだがな
Understood.
俺の能力を知りながら 生きている奴は。 ブック！ あ？ あっちのペースに 巻き込まれちゃダメだ！
So their goal is to eradicate the Ants,
leaving the Hunters Association
俺は　問答無用でカードを奪うって やり方は嫌いだ。
to take the blame.
だから　約束しろ 先に「参った」って言ったほうが
I must make this fast...
持ってるカードを全部 相手に渡すって。
Before my heart is swayed.
これは最後の譲歩だ。
King...
約束がなければ　ただの強奪。 そんな奴に 死んでもカードは渡さない！
We are both in difficult positions.
器用な奴だ
100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva!
だが　オーラの攻防力移動は かなり　お粗末 よくも　まぁ デカい口をたたいたもんだ
First Hand!
まぁ　それは　もういい 俺が言いたいのは
That's...
計画通り
I can't sense anyone else fighting.
決定的な力量の差を 見せつけられたら
Does that mean I'm the only one left?
奴をおびき寄せる行動 開始だわよ！
Youpi!
オス！
Pouf!
…って言いたいところだけど
You've changed a lot since I last saw you.
やられっ放しは やっぱり　ムカつく
I could say the same to you.
使わせてやる 作戦は　それからだ！
I had to escape without alerting the enemy.
フン…　もう少し痛い目に 遭いたいようだな！
And if I move all my dispersed particles
at once, it's too conspicuous.
チッ。 使って来い ひと泡　吹かせてやる！
Well, I suppose you have your own concerns...
…って面してるぜ 使わねえよ！
You've grown up.
ガキが！
I have no conclusive proof
思ったより　すばしっこいぜ
that the change in Pitou will
actually benefit the King...
「トランスフォーム」で 別のカードにしてたってことか？ 「アカンパニー」オン！ ソウフラビへ！
Through his own experiences,
Youpi could understand Pitou's behavior.
「アカンパニー」？　なぜ？
Youpi...
何で　こんな 面倒なまねをしてまで
This was a test.
俺とサシになりたかったのか。 理由は１つ。
Which made it very clear to Youpi
あんたが他の２人に 助けを求めたら　面倒でしょ？ はぁ？ ますます　意味分かんねえ。
that Pouf was fearful of the subtle changes
バカだね。
Pitou and Youpi had undergone.
あぁ…！
A foolish question.
ハハハ！
We must go to the King at once!
軽いねぇ　攻撃が！ おめぇには　俺は倒せねえよ！
And that's all there is to it... Right?
手加減しねえぞ　恨むなよ。
His response was entirely sincere. Indeed.
フフフ… 先に言われちゃったわね。 あぁ！
He was concerned only with
leaving as soon as possible.
思い出に　一発 打たせてやることにしているの。 元に戻ると うまく手加減できなくて…。
Because Youpi was feeling the same fear.
ん？
I'm sure that was a direct hit...
聞いてないか…。
He's tough!
体術や筋力は　俺がやや上 だけど　オーラの量は はるかに俺が劣る
A good attack. I could not anticipate it.
通常の攻撃じゃ 恐らくダメージは与えられない
Are you satisfied now?
うっ！ クソっ　拳の痛みが 頭の芯まで響く
He still wants me to sit with him?
余裕こいてる暇ねえな
I shall not repeat myself.
でも数秒は 動きを止められるな ＯＫ　実験　その２
Third Hand!
行くぜ。 何を仕込んでやがる…
I can no longer back down!
俺の兄貴に特注した 超合金ヨーヨー。 重さ５０ｋｇくらいあるから 食らったら　効くぜ！
Are you really so eager to die?
クソっ！
From the King's perspective, the wrath that was unleashed
遠心力と重さで　とんでもねえ 攻撃力になってやがる！
was no stronger than that
of a child throwing a fit.
奴は　俺が特定の攻撃を 仕掛けた時　必ず右側が空く
Yet it was violent enough to induce
Netero to more than double the distance
ヨーヨーを奪い 奴の両手をフリーにすれば…
between the King and him.
その癖は　必ず顔を出す！
It was an insult likened to laughing off
あっ！　チッ！ 勝機！
Netero's declaration that
そこだ！
he would not back down.
よし！　あばら粉砕コース！
Come on...
うわ！ あれ？　ヨーヨー２個あるって 言わなかったっけ？
You will only influence me by using words.
うわ…。
Damned newborn brat.
う…。 うわっ　まだ意識あんの？ おっさんさ　蹴る時 反対側の腕のガード上がるよね？
If it were that simple,
I wouldn't have to do this!
その死角を利用して
Wait...
ヨーヨーを取り出し 攻撃したってのか？
By using...
それじゃ　お前の防御の癖も？
words?
左足のミドルを 誘うためのフェイク。
King...
１個目のヨーヨーを 離したのも…？
Would you like to know your name?
「アカンパニー」で 仲間から離れたのは？ １対１を意識させて
How would you know my name?
信じられねえ　今の短い攻防で ３つも罠を仕掛けやがるとは。 ３つ？　冗談だろ。
My subordinates were present at the
moment of your mother's passing.
動き全てが罠だぜ。 うわ！
She uttered your name with her dying breath.
うわ!! 実験終了！　どっちもいけるね。
And my subordinates may have died
fighting your Royal Guard by now.
いいかげん　認めたらどうだ？
Interested in fighting me now?
全然　俺は… 参ってない！
If you can force me to admit defeat, I will tell you your name.
俺は　勘違いしてたな
Force you to admit defeat without killing you?
俺の能力…　お見せしよう。
So, similar to a bishop and rook handicap...
勝つためなら 意地を捨て　理をとる！
No matter.
悟らせてやろう
I shall checkmate you shortly.